[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "U.S. hockey star Buzz Schneider was played by his own son in the movie Miracle.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the terrorists technology expert in Die Hard?", "correct_answer": "Theo", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeff", "Karl", "Charles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what form is gold added to some expensive dishes, especially sweets and drinks?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Gold leaf", "Gold flakes", "Gold dust"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Both male and female mammals have the ability to produce milk.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dont call me Shirley is a quote from this movie.", "correct_answer": "Airplane!", "incorrect_answers": ["The Terminal", "Airport", "Air Force One"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the infamous pool scene in the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High involving Linda and Brad, what color is Lindas bikini?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "White", "Black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Sixteen Candles, Farmer Ted ends up getting together with Jake Ryans girlfriend. They wake up in the back seat of Jakes fathers car. What kind of car is it?", "correct_answer": "Rolls Royce", "incorrect_answers": ["Cadillac", "Corvette", "Jaguar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The states of Arizona, Utah, New Mexico and Colorado form an exception to what important mathematical theorem?", "correct_answer": "Four Color Theorem", "incorrect_answers": ["Continuum Theorem", "Fermats Last  Theorem", "Goldbachs Theorem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the scientific (Latin) name of the wild carrot?", "correct_answer": "Daucus carota", "incorrect_answers": ["Neee wassupdoc", "Noctus viseus", "Carota carota"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country is the grizzly bear listed as a threatened species?", "correct_answer": "U.S.", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Canada", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movies does Rambo fight the Russians?", "correct_answer": "Rambo III and First Blood pt. II", "incorrect_answers": ["First Blood and First Blood pt. II", "He doesnt fight the Russians.", "Rambo III and Rambo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dog Day Afternoon, Sonny asks his partner what country he wants to go to. What does his partner say?", "correct_answer": "Wyoming", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Algeria", "Spain"]}]